<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GPCET College</string>
    <string name="about_college">About College</string>
    <string name="title_activity_aboutcollege">Aboutcollege</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "G. Pullaiah College of Engineering and Technology, Kurnool has been established in the"
        "year 2007 and is run by Sri Sai Krishna Educational Society founded by devoted Pioneer duo"
        "in the field of education Sri G. Pullaiah and his son Sri G.V.M Mohan Kumar, both having a"
        "long and outstanding experience in educational system with the motto "Pioneering Innovative"
        "Education". It is one of the best colleges to acquire an Engineering degree because it "
        "stands out unique in every aspect starting from infrastructure to the labs and from faculty"
        "to the Trainings being imparted to the students. It started as a regular Engineering "
        "college unlike others and now it is an Autonomous college where it has become the student's"
        "first choice with 100% admissions every year in the entire state of Andhra Pradesh."
"GPCET is a prestigious Autonomous Engineering college offering Six B. Tech programs"
        "Computer Science and Engineering, Computer Science and Engineering (Artificial Intelligence)",
        "Electronics and Communication Engineering, Electrical and Electronics Engineering, "
        "Mechanical Engineering, Civil Engineering and three M. Tech programmes in Engineering and "
        "MBA (Master of Business Administration). The institute is approved by AICTE, New Delhi "
        "besides being affiliated to Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University Anantapur (JNTUA). "
        "It has also been accredited by National Assessment and Accreditation Council (NAAC) with "
        "'A' Grade along with UGC recognition under Sections 2(f) and 12(B) of the UGC Act. Four "
        "B. Tech programs have been accredited by National Board of Accreditation (NBA), New Delhi."
"Features:"
"• International Certification Programs"
"• Flexible Academics"
"• Smart Classrooms"
"• Expert Faculty"
"• Comfortable Transport Facility"
"• Advanced Engineering Labs"

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cse">CSE</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cse_fac">CSE_FAC</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ece_fac">ece_fac</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contentscrolling3">contentscrolling3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_civil_fac">civil_fac</string>
    <string name="title_activity_content_scrolling6">content_scrolling6</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mech_fac">Mech_fac</string>
</resources>